Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Get your bag off the table.
People eat there.
They eat on plates.
Don't give me any crap,
Maizy.
l'm telling.
You said "crap."
There's nothing
wrong with crap.
Oh, really?
l thought that was a swear.
No.
You're thinking of shit.
Oh, right.
Do you mind?
A sixth grader
chased me on his bike,
and l was running.
When l got
exhausted and fell down,
he whaled me with his shoe.
Thank your parents for that.
How come?
lt was their brilliant
idea to move here.
They weren't making
enough cash in lndianapolis.
Forget that we were
perfectly happy.
So thank them for getting
treated like shit every day.
l'm telling on that one.
Shut your face.
Your book bag
doesn't go on the floor.
Always have a cow.
Your nails are digging
to my arm, God damn it!
Pick it up.
You're just supposed to
open the door for us.
You're not supposed to
kick us around.
l'm an American,
l have rights.
Maizy, did l kick you around?
No, but you said "shit" twice.
But only once for real.
l've got better things
to do than babysit you,
you little stain.
Like what?
Hang out with
friends you don't have?
Why don't you just shut up?
Want to make me?
When our mother figure
isn't here, l'm in charge.
l'm sick of you
calling her that!
Too bad.
You moron !
l don't know why
we need boys at all.
They're so loud.
Shut up!
Shut up yourself!
We need boys
so they can grow up,
get married,
and turn into shadows.
Let the dog out.
Percy!
This is such
a wonderful dinner, Mother.
How do you find the time?
Miles.
Maizy, put that down.
Did you win in
hockey yesterday?
Hockey's been
over for two weeks.
l guess you don't
want a hockey stick
for your birthday.
You know what?
When Dad goes to New York,
l'm going to take a week
off work.
So you can interview
new housekeepers?
l've had enough
of your ugliness.
Oh, really?
Mmm-hmm.
We're all just
a little tired
of the act.
This was a really good idea.
Thank you.
How's that pie?
Not bad.
You gonna be at work
in the morning?
l don't see
how l can avoid it.
You don't seem
very happy about it.
All right,
if you gotta know,
l'm really not that excited
about working for
my girlfriend.
There. l said it.
lt's out of the way.
Okay, okay.
Buck, l love you.
l can't help myself.
l wanna get married,
l wanna have a family.
l wanna do it with you.
Well, you know, the clock
is ticking away here.
l would just like to
hear the pitter-patter
of tiny feet before l die.
l'll get you a mouse
and a piece of sheet metal.
Come on.
Lighten up, will you?
Don't push my button.
l'm not gonna get into this.
l'm not pushing your buttons.
l know me,
l know what l like.
All right?
l like my friends.
l like my freedom.
l like knowing
l can throw my sticks
in the trunk of my car
and go golfing
anytime l want.
l don't hurt anybody.
l don't see
what the problem is.
That's the best formula
for loneliness l ever heard.
Why are we arguing?
We're talking.
l said l'd be at work
in the morning.
l'll be there.
Okay.
l. . . l just
gotta get this out.
l mean, l know l'm harping
on something here, but,
you know,
just let me say it.
l mean, you know, l am. . .
l'm working on history.
l'm working on the past.
You're gonna show up for work,
you swear to God?
ln the A.M.? Promise?
Chanice,
l'll be honest with you,
if l could
think of an excuse
that you would buy,
l'd use it.
(RlNGlNG)
Hello.
Oh, God.
What?
Just a second.
lt's your aunt.
What happened?
Your Dad had a heart attack.
Who's going to
watch the kids?
Marcie.
She's right
across the street.
She's the last person
l'd ask for a favor.
What about the Nevilles?
Would you call them?
l want to leave
as soon as we can.
l am so helpless here.
Honey, now,
don't start getting
down on why we moved.
lt has nothing to
do with what happened.
Sorry.
Now, this is just a thought.
What about Buck?
l'm sure he'd be
glad to help out.
This is not the time
to discuss your brother.
l don't want him here.
lt's just a suggestion.
He doesn't have kids.
He isn't married.
He doesn't even work!
He's a little out there,
but he's responsible,
and he's family.
Buck isn't the kind of guy
l feel comfortable leaving
my kids with.
The trashy people
he hangs out with.
That woman who sells tires.
The horse racing.
The gambling.
Can you see him in this house?
Okay.
Call the Nevilles.
Are we going to lndianapolis?
Daddy and l are.
And we're not?
No. l don't think
that would be a good idea.
Thanks.
l love my father very much.
So why did you
move away from him?
lf my whole family
moved away from me,
l'd have a heart attack, too.
Oh, l see.
Who gonna take care of us?
Mr. and Mrs. Neville.
ls that a joke?
You don't like the Nevilles?
Their dog's a ball sniffer.
Don't talk like that.
Mr. Neville yelled
at Michael Larson
because the dog was
sniffing Michael's balls.
Don't use that word.
l don't know another word.
Well, l'm sure we can talk
to Mr. Neville about the dog.
Sorry, honey.
They're in Florida.
Okay. You get in bed.
You have to get up
for school.
Who's in Florida?
Get back in bed.
What's another word
for "balls"?
Get in bed.
"Nuts."
What do we do?
l don't think
we have much choice.
Can we trust him?
Yeah?
Buck, this is Bob.
Bob.
Bob who?
Buck, it's your brother.
Bobby.
Bobby,
hang on a minute.
(BUCK COUGHlNG)
(ALARMS BLARlNG)
Bobby, l just used
your Christmas present.
Oh, the clapper.
Bobby, you little piss ant,
how you doing?
Jeez. What are you, drunk?
Hey, you know something?
We gotta get together.
l haven't been
over to your house
since you moved.
Hey...
I'm reaI sorry
about those bushes too.
l had no idea they would
all catch on fire like that.
You know, you were right.
l should never have
put the barbecue that close.
Buck, Cindy's father
had a heart attack tonight.
We'd like to get down to
lndianapolis as soon as
possible,
but we have a problem
with the kids.
We're stuck for somebody
to watch them.
lf you're not doing
anything. . .
ls this okay with Cindy?
This has got her approval
on it?
Oh, yeah.
That would be great!
l'd be honored ! Sure!
l've still got
the one bedroom, you know,
l'm gonna get a bigger place,
but they bring their
sleeping bags over here,
we'll have some fun.
We'll make tents and stuff.
We'll get some toys
and some peanut butter.
l thought you could come here.
The kids have school.
What am l thinking about?
Sure.
Do we wanna do this tonight
or in the morning?
Tonight would be best, l mean,
if you could do it.
Yeah. Tonight will be fine.
That'll be fine.
Don't worry about it.
l'll pack a few things.
l'm on my way.
Thanks. See you soon.
He can do it.
He was asleep,
and l woke him up.
At this hour,
that's a good sign.
We're all set.
Okay. This, this, this.
Bag, bag, bag.
Okay.
This one will do. This. . .
(RlNGlNG)
Hello.
Chanice? Honey?
Honey, l have some bad news.
Let me guess.
You are not coming in
to work in the morning.
Just let. . .
Let. . .
No, but. . .
You don't. . .
Would you just. . . Let me. . .
Give me. . .
You're not. . .
Give me a. . .
Goodbye.
Oh, boy. Those kids.
l haven't seen those
kids in a while.
Tia's got to be nine.
Nine, maybe ten. Oh, boy.
And the two new ones,
they're. . .
Larry and. . .
Betsy.
Betsy. . .
Jennifer. Jennifer.
Larry and Jennifer.
Nice kids.
Honey, he's 40 years old.
He knows his way around.
Look, why don't
you go finish packing,
and l'll watch out for Buck?
What the hell?
Where is everybody?
Bob!
Bob?
This isn't funny!
Come on ! Wake up!
l'm freezing
my ass off out here!
Oh, shit.
Come on,
l'm getting mad, Bob.
Yo, Bobby!
Buck?
Bob?
Buck!
Over here!
(DOGS BARKlNG)
You have any idea
how many big white houses
there are on this street?
What?
Keep it down.
What do you want me
to do with my car?
MAN: For crying out loud !
Sorry, Mr. Hatfield !
lt's 2:00 a.m. !
How you doing?
Hey, sorry l'm late.
Oh, no, hey, come in.
What happened to the mustache?
Thanks for coming.
Had to shave it off.
How's Cindy?
Not well. Not well.
Her dad?
Hard to say.
All those medical terms, huh?
What is it, an infarction or
something like that?
Hey, l stopped
smoking cigarettes.
Oh, good.
lsn't that something?
l'm on to cigars now.
l'm onto a five-year plan.
l eliminated the cigarettes,
then l go to cigars,
then l go to pipes,
then to chewing tobacco,
then l'm onto that
nicotine gum.
Good.
Yeah.
Money.
l'll leave you blank checks.
No, please.
l've got lots of money.
No!
No, please.
No.
Look, l've got the money.
Please, l'd like to do this,
all right?
So. . .
No.
No, come on, will you?
Please. . .
Okay.
l'll pay you back
when we get home.
l won't have any problems
cashing
a second-party
out-of-state paycheck, will l?
The reason l'm saying is,
l've been so busy lately,
l haven't been
able to do my banking.
l don't think
there will be a problem.
Don't worry about it.
Let me just
leave you the checks.
Well, only if it's
comfortable for you.
That'll be easier.
l guess, sure.
Do you have a plunger here?
While l'm thinking of these
things.
For the morning, you know?
My plumbing is just so bad.
Of course, yours is good
plumbing here, right?
Yeah. l would imagine. . .
Don't worry about it.
You know,
everything will be fine.
Just been bound up lately.
lt's driving me crazy.
l've been eating
a lot of cheese,
for some reason.
l don't know what it is,
l've got a craving for
the stuff.
Think maybe that's
an allergy or something?
Yeah.
l don't know.
l can't get enough cheese.
l feel like a big mouse.
l don't know.
Ah, well. Ah, well.
Let's see. . .
Oh, Miles' birthday.
Forget that.
We'll be back by that time.
Okay, then.
This should do.
l probably won't
use any of them.
Just in case.
Right.
Great. Okay.
Here we go.
l know
l've forgotten something.
Just put. . .
What else? What else?
Right up. There you go.
All right?
Okay. That looks nice.
Here. Give me your arm.
There you go.
This should only
be a few days,
and l promise
l'll call you tomorrow.
BOB: You got all
the phone numbers, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, we're off.
All right,
you take care of yourself.
Thanks a lot, Buck.
Okay. All right.
We really appreciate it.
Thanks. Thanks.
All right.
Thank you.
Say hi to your dad for me.
You can do it.
Drive safe, all right?
Okay, now.
Okay.
(WHlSTLES)
Boy, that's for sure.
Unbreakable.
Shit.
lt's 7:02 in the A.M. , you're
listening to W-l-don't-have
-to-go-to-work-today,
brought to you
by Kobolowski Tires.
For the best in tires,
see Chanice Kobolowski.
(UPBEAT SONG PLAYlNG)
(SlNGlNG ALONG)
Tia!
You remember me?
Uncle Buck.
The Uncle Buck.
Coffee drinker, huh?
Hungry?
No.
Oh, come on, sure you are.
Everybody loves breakfast.
You've got to
have a good breakfast,
start the day off right.
Mmm.
So where are the other ones?
Other ones what?
The other kids.
They have names.
Miles and Maizy.
Are Miles and Maizy up yet?
l woke them, thank you.
There you go.
Are you deaf?
l said l wasn't hungry.
That's one of my specialties.
l'd rather starve,
thank you.
Does your mom know
you drink coffee?
l'm not doing it
to impress you.
l appreciate that.
ls there any particular reason
why you're giving me such
a hard time?
Am l giving you a hard time?
Well, l don't know.
Hey! How you doing?
Who are you?
l'm your Uncle Buck.
Do l have an uncle?
Unfortunately.
Holy smokes.
He's cooking our garbage.
Hey, where's your sister. . .
Her name is Maizy. . .
Maizy.
. . .for the second time.
Sorry.
You must be hungry.
Just for you.
Oh, my God.
He put onions in the eggs.
l'll gonna go check on Maizy.
l'll fix you some cereal
when l get back.
Can l ask you something?
What?
ls your sister
always this pleasant?
No. She's usually in
a bad mood in the morning.
Ow!
Do you want
knots in your hair?
Ow!
Cut it out.
l want Mom to do it.
Mom's not here.
She is too.
No, she's not.
She and Dad
went to lndianapolis.
They did not.
Okay, they didn't.
They did?
Yes. l'm taking care of you.
But you can't drive?
Where do you live?
The city.
Do you have a house?
Apartment.
Own or rent?
Rent.
What do you do?
Lots of things.
Where's your office?
l don't have one.
How come?
l don't need one.
Where's your wife?
Don't have one.
How come?
lt's a long story.
Do you have kids?
No, l don't.
How come?
lt's an even longer story.
Are you my dad's brother?
What's your record for
consecutive questions asked?
38.
l'm your dad's brother
all right.
You have more hair
on your nose than Dad.
Nice of you to notice.
l'm a kid. That's my job.
That's my car.
That isn't my car.
(SCREAMlNG)
Tying your shoe?
What time do you
want me to pick you up
after school?
Don't bother.
l'll get a ride
with friends.
No. l've got my orders.
What time?
Are you really this stupid?
l said l would get a ride.
l always get a ride.
l'll just call the school,
find out what time,
and l'll meet you right here.
Go ahead. Call the school.
l won't be here.
Stand me up today,
and tomorrow
l'll drive you to school in
my robe and pajamas and walk
you to your first class.
4:00, okay?
l'm stunned that
l'm related to you.
You get the pole
out of your keister,
we'll get along just fine.
Did you ever have anyone
embarrass you like this?
No.
You think she hates me?
With a passion.
Really.
You think it's the hat?
No.
No?
A lot of people hate this hat.
lt angers a lot of people,
just the sight of it.
l'll tell you a story
about that on the way
to school.
Uh-huh. Yeah, right.
Listen, Buck.
For eight years,
you have been making plans
and breaking plans.
What are you talking about,
hon?
Didn't we talk last night?
Didn't we talk last night
about this?
What did we talk about?
Me playing the father.
l'm glad that you can
do it for your brother.
You sure as hell
can't do it for me.
How could l do it for you,
hon?
We don't have kids.
What are you talking about?
Buck, l know you think
the job is pointless,
and in some way,
l'm trying to
manipulate you,
and control you
and ruin your life.
No.
Look, l have to
fill the position.
lt's important
to the company,
it's important to me.
l'm swamped down here.
Now, unless you
tell me different,
l'm offering the job
to somebody else.
Why don't you give me
a week to think about it.
You know, 'cause
l don't know how long
l'm gonna be here, hon.
And, you know,
if during that week
you see somebody in there
that's gonna fill the bill,
hire him, part-time basis
or whatever.
And that way, you know,
l'll make up my mind,
and you know,
we'll see where
we are at that point.
Okay. Well, l have to go!
Bye-bye, hon.
Eight. Eight more. Come on.
Work it.
Get the circulation going.
Come on. Step it up.
Isn't peace wonderfuI?
Mikhail Gorbachev,
the most improbabIe
eviI emperor in captivity,
captivates Manhattan,
wows the UN,
by announcing a uniIateraI
cut in the Soviet military,
smiles and waves
with erstwhile cold warriors
RonaId Reagan...
(WHlNES)
The stock market has
its best week since JuIy.
Take that Karl Marx.
(SNORlNG)
Would you like to talk
about a possible lunch trade?
Cover your ears.
What?
Just do it.
(CAR BACKFlRES)
Do you know
how whipped an engine
has to be to blow that loud?
Call me.
You ever hear of a tune-up?
(CHUCKLlNG)
(LAUGHS MOCKlNGLY)
You ever hear
of a ritual killing?
(CONTlNUES MOCKlNG)
l don't get it.
You gnaw on her face
in public like that again,
and you'll be one.
Hey!
Are you crazy?
l can be.
You could have
taken his head off!
Yeah, but would he notice?
Can we get
something straight?
The guy's a predator,
and you're his prey.
Oh, really.
You bet.
And how do you know?
When l was his age,
l was the guy
zooming the girls like you.
Pretty face,
big chip on your shoulder.
l recommend that you
stay out of my personal life.
Do your parents stay out
of your personal life?
They don't know
my personal life.
Have they met twiddle dink?
His name is Bug.
(SCOFFS)
First or last?
First.
What's his last name, Spray?
You should talk, Buck.
No.
No. N-O.
Don't look at me like that.
Don't.
That's not fair.
Don't you have
a favorite doll
or something?
Why don't we get
one of your dolls
and put your dad's
pajamas on him?
No.
Your brother!
What about your brother?
How about the dog?
You know the dog.
You can't.
You just can't.
lt's a new law.
That's it.
lt's in the books.
You don't want
to sleep with me.
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Can somebody get that,
please?
Do l have to do
everything around here?
MlLES: Yo.
ClNDY:
Hi, sweetie. How are you?
Fine. l'm earning my keep.
Uncle Buck's got me
busting my hump.
He says a little hard work
will put hair on my chest.
At least
l'm learning a trade.
That's good.
Grandpa's feeling
a little bit better.
And he sent you
big hugs and kisses.
Tell him to hang in there.
Can you get Uncle Buck?
Will do, chickie.
Mom.
Hi.
Next time you take off,
why don't you hire
a murderer to watch the house?
This guy's a joke.
Well, why don't you
just go your way
and let him go his.
While he systematically
dismantles my life.
Another drawback
is l'm a big drooler.
You could wake up
in the middle
of the night
thinking you were
asleep in a swamp.
Mom's on the phone.
Oh, good.
l'll be right there.
The guy took off and
left Miles and Maizy alone.
Plus. . .he drinks.
Did you brush
your teeth?
Yeah.
You can feel
my toothbrush.
l have a friend
who works at the crime
lab at the police station.
l could give him
your toothbrush
and he could run
a test on it to see if you
actually brushed your teeth
or just ran your toothbrush
under the faucet.
lf that's true,
we're gonna really have to
start brushing our teeth.
Hi. How are you?
ClNDY: I'm okay.
How's everything?
Good. Good.
You sure?
Everything is fine here.
Everything is fine.
Kids are okay?
Kids are great!
We're having
a great time together.
How's your dad?
He's okay. He's okay.
He's getting better.
Thanks.
Good. Well, that's good news.
That's encouraging.
I've got a reaI
good feeIing about this.
He's gonna be fine.
l've got a few questions
for you.
You know, you got
an interesting set of pIates
in the Iiving room there.
Are they oId?
Yeah.
They are.
Where would you find
something like that?
ln an antique shop
downtown or something?
ln England.
(WHlSTLES)
Everything eIse seems...
How many times a day
do you feed a dog
like that?
How many times a day
do you think he eats?
Four or five.
l should have told you
that he eats once.
He eats once a day.
Just once.
What does he like
to drink? Water?
Yes. He drinks water.
l'd keep some water out.
l've been leaving
the toilet seats up.
Yeah.
ls that what
the blue water is?
lt's not good for him.
(GROANS) Oh, God.
That might account
for something.
Nothing.
Just an odd coloration
out on the grass.
Buck, um. . .
l just want you to know
it makes me feel very secure
to know that you're there.
(CRYlNG)
Thank you very much.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Bob!
(SlGHS)
Cindy.
Come on. Open up.
Hello.
BUCK: l'm getting mad.
All right.
Get ready. Here l come.
Come on.
What? Do l have
to talk dirty to you?
Come on,
open up for daddy.
There we go.
Come on.
Nice and easy.
Come on, there we go.
Ah ! Take that!
Take that!
Come on ! You don't want
the crowbar, do you?
Come on !
Open up!
l'm going to
shove my load into you
whether you like it or not.
Come on ! (GROANS)
Come on,
you son of a bitch.
Open up.
Okay. (SlGHS)
(SCREAMlNG)
Freeze!
What?
Who are you?
Cindy!
She's in lndianapolis.
What's she doing
in lndianapolis?
Her father had a heart attack.
Who are you?
And how do you know
her father had a heart attack?
l'm her brother-in-law.
Oh, yeah !
Who you talking dirty to?
The washing machine.
l. . .
l don't know
how to work it,
so l was kicking it
and swearing at it,
you know, which is not
an uncommon thing to do.
And you thought that. . .
(CHUCKLlNG) Oh, jeez. . .
l apologize.
Okay.
Boy! That's funny.
l live across the street.
My name is Marcie.
Buck Russell.
Marcie Dahlgren-Frost.
Dahlgren is my maiden name.
Frost is my married name.
l'm single again,
but l never bothered
to lose the Frost.
And l get compliments
on the hyphen.
Sure you would.
Yeah.
Well, l came
to invite Cindy
to lunch.
But since she's not here,
do you have plans?
Actually, l got a lot
of things to do around here.
Rain check?
l'll only be here
a couple days.
Cindy said it would
only be a couple days?
Well, she didn't specify.
l just assumed, you know.
My father's heart attack,
l was out of town
for three weeks.
No wonder Cindy
didn't call me.
You need a relative
for an imposition this size.
Waiting for your sex?
Shut up.
Tia.
What did you blow
all that make-up for?
We're just going bowling.
l'm not going bowling.
Come on, it's a great sport.
And it's virtually
impossible to get pregnant
while doing it.
lf you catch my drift.
You're disgusting.
l'll die before
l go anywhere with you.
lt's gonna be fun.
They have rent-a-shoes.
And rent-a-foot-disease.
We've done
the battle of the wills.
The deck's stacked
in my favor.
You're just gonna
lose again.
Try me.
How'd you like to spend
the next several nights
wondering if your crazy
out-of-work bum uncle
will shave your head
while you sleep?
See you in the car.
(EERlE MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(MlMlCS SHAVER BUZZlNG)
Yeah !
There you go.
Now, this is
a bowling ball.
How you doing?
l've never seen you
here before.
l know about everybody.
That's why
they call me Pal.
Buy you a beer?
You must be
a college student, right?
Cheerleader, probably.
You look firm.
Come on. Give it a push.
You like all-terrain vehicles?
l got a brand-new
Bronco right out in
the parking lot. Red.
Want to go for a ride?
Maizy,
if the object
of the game were
to get the ball
as close to the pins
without knocking any over,
you would be champion
of the world.
Really?
Really.
My throat sort of hurts.
l can't talk.
l got a cure for that.
Buck.
You got a game somewhere, Pal?
Yeah.
You won't get any strikes
sitting there, are you?
Move it!
Go on, get out!
Hey, shithead !
Where the hell
you been, huh?
(BOTH VOCALlZlNG)
BOTH: Hey! Hey! Hey!
Come on, sit down.
l want you
to meet my niece.
Tia, this is Rog.
Rog, Tia.
Hi. How are you?
E. Roger Coswell.
Come on.
lt ain't gonna bite.
Okay. You've got to let
somebody know where you are.
l've been checking
car trunks for your corpse.
Yeah, l'm sorry
about that.
l've been out in the suburbs
looking after my brother's
kids for a few days.
They're cute!
Oh, l tell you.
Art Linkletter was right,
kids do say
the god damnedest things.
ls Chanice here?
No. l'm kinda
flying solo tonight.
l want to let her have it
for not marrying you.
You know, if she caged you
and married your
worthless butt,
l'd be able to find you.
l got to talk business.
l can't find you.
Why don't we step
in my office, then?
Excuse us, will you.
Come on.
lt was nice meeting you.
l'll remember it always.
Cute kid.
Jimmy Bean called.
Oh, yeah?
He's coming in
for the Winter Million
at Burlington Park
on Friday.
He says it's a boat race.
Very easy money.
He owes you
and he owes me.
So he says
we should show up
an hour before post time
and he'll
give us the tip.
Consider this, Buck,
with this score,
your whole year's covered.
Huh?
Maybe l can make it work.
l'll see you Friday night.
Thanks, Rog.
Watch the sterno,
will you?
Hey,
watch your fingers.
Yay!
What's a Chanice?
That's someone
who's sometimes
seen around a Buck.
Your girlfriend?
A friend, and, yes,
she is a girl.
Are you supposed
to marry her or something?
The subject has come up, yes,
but nothing serious.
Maybe if you got married,
you'd stop being
such an asshole.
Cigar?
No, thanks.
Let me know if
you change your mind.
l will.
l'll get it nice
and juicy for you.
This is
where you separate
the men from the boys.
Easy. Easy.
There you go. Yeah.
l got you now.
Happy birthday!
Whoo!
l hope you're hungry.
You should see the toast!
l couldn't even
get it through the door.
Ah, announcement here.
There's going to be
a little delay on the clown.
What clown?
Miles' mom hired a clown.
(EXCLAlMS)
(BREATHlNG HEAVlLY)
(GROANS)
(BELCHES)
What's the matter?
You don't like clowns?
(DOORBELL RlNGlNG)
Yeah. About five years ago.
Clowns are so boring,
they make me puke.
(MUMBLlNG)
Screw them.
That's all they get.
(LAUGHlNG)
l'm Pooter-The-Clown.
Put it there.
(HONKS)
The kids will love that.
l didn't order you.
My sister-in-law did.
She's not here right now.
l'm looking after them.
l'm the uncle.
l'm Buck Russell.
Great, listen,
l'm sorry l'm late.
l was
at this all-night
bachelorette party.
Need any dildo jokes?
Wham ! l'm the guy!
What did you have?
A few drinks this morning?
Huh? l think you did,
didn't you?
Who are you?
Mother Cabrini?
You never
touch the stuff?
No, no, no,
but l wouldn't be drinking
if l was going to
entertain some kids.
l don't have
to take any shit
from you.
You know who l am?
ln the field of
local live home
entertainment,
l'm a God !
Get in your mouse
and get out of here.
Hey, you, let me
tell you something,
you low-life, lying,
four-flushing sack of shit.
(GROWLS)
Let's go out
to the car, huh?
Why?
What do you mean,
why?
Not now.
lt's fine.
lt's not fine.
Why not?
l just don't
feel right yet.
You ever going
to feel right?
l don't get
where we're going.
l told you 25 times.
We're going to pick up Tia.
She's at
a cheerleader's house
having dinner.
Well, so she says.
Since when do cheerleaders
live in the woods?
Come on.
l'll take you home now.
l don't want to go home.
l'm okay.
Sure?
Trust me.
(CAR BACKFlRES)
Shit!
Well, well, well.
They certainly are scraping
the bottom of the barrel
for cheerleaders these days.
What are you doing here?
We were just driving by,
going out for some ice cream.
Thought you might
like to join us.
l said l would
be home at 1 0:00.
lt's not even 9:00.
Who said anything about that?
l just thought you'd like
to join us for some ice cream.
Maybe your Bug here
can join us.
We can talk about
burying the hatchet.
You know what
a hatchet is,
don't you, Bug?
lt's an ax?
Sort of. Yeah. Yeah.
l got one in the car
if you'd like to see it.
l'll pass.
Fair enough.
l like to carry it.
You never know
when you're gonna need it.
A situation
may come up, say,
for example, someone's been
drinking and about to drive
a loved one home,
then l like
to know l have it.
Not to kill.
(CHUCKLES)
Just to maim.
Take a little
off the shoulder. Woosh !
The elbow.
Shave a little meat
off the old kneecap.
Whoo.
You got both kneecaps?
l like to keep mine
razor-sharp, too.
Sharp enough
you can shave with them.
Why, l've been known
to circumcise a gnat.
You're not a gnat,
are you, Bug?
Wait a minute.
Bug, gnat.
ls there a little
similarity there?
Whoa! l think there is.
You understand
what l'm talking about?
l don't think you do.
l'll be right back.
l'm sorry.
Look, um, l think
you'd better split.
You know, l don't
exactly want him going
berserk with an ax on me.
He's all talk.
Here it is.
Come on over. Come on,
l wanna show it to you.
Maybe later.
Okay.
He's gone in a few days.
Just relax.
l'll get him back.
That's a pretty stupid thing
to do during flu season.
l bet she's getting
the tongue.
BUCK: Just looking.
Next.
Tell you what.
Let me go in
there first, okay?
l'll cover for you,
give you a little more
time out here to relax.
Okay. Mmm.
All right?
Good morning.
l'm Anita Hoargarth.
Buck Melanoma,
Moley Russell's wart.
Not her wart,
not her wart.
l'm the wart.
She's my tumor,
my growth, my. . .my pimple.
l'm "Uncle Wart."
Buck "Wart" Russell,
that's what they call me.
Or melanoma head.
They'll call me that.
"Melanoma head's" coming.
l'm. . . Uncle,
Maizy Russell's uncle.
Her uncle.
Her mother set up
this conference with you.
l'm assistant
principal here,
as you've probably noticed
from the indications
on the door.
This door?
The outer door. Yes.
The outer door.
There's nothing on this one.
That's just about
enough of that.
Sorry.
l've been an educator
for 31 .3 years,
and in that time,
l've seen a lot
of bad eggs.
l say "eggs" because
at the elementary level,
we are not dealing with
fully developed individuals.
l see a bad egg
when l look
at your niece.
She is a twiddler,
a dreamer, a silly heart.
She is a jabberbox.
And frankly. . .
l don't think she takes
a thing in her life or her
career as a student seriously.
She's only six.
That is not
a valid excuse!
l hear that every day
and l dismiss it.
l don't think
l want to know
a six-year-old
who isn't a dreamer,
or a silly heart.
And l sure don't want to
know one who takes their
student career seriously.
l don't have a college degree
l don't even have a job.
Does anyone have a special
story about something
that happened this week?
Maizy.
My uncle was
microwaving my socks,
and the dog
threw up on the couch
for about an hour.
Honest?
Yes.
Why was your uncle
microwaving your socks?
He can't get the goddamn
washing machine to work.
Blasphemer!
BUCK: l know a good kid
when l see one.
Because they're
all good kids
until dried-out,
brain-dead skags
like you
drag them down
and convince them
they're no good.
You so much as scowl
at my niece or any other
kid in this school
and l hear about it,
l'm coming looking for you.
Take this quarter.
Go downtown, and have a rat
gnaw that thing off your face.
(GASPS)
Good day to you, madam.
Next.
Ah, yeah !
TERRY: Hi, Chanice.
This is Terry.
Walt Bern...
Jesus, would you
get with the program.
Bernstein is his name.
I forgot to give you
the message.
At least somebody knows
what they're doing down there.
BUCK: Chanice? Buck.
I hate these machines.
Look, I'm just caIIing
to say I miss you.
I know you probabIy
don't believe it,
but it's true.
No, I haven't been drinking.
I've been thinking
a Iot about you
and what we've talked about
the past few weeks.
I think about you
all the time.
I think about those
two dimpIes on your buns.
Dimples.
What did we call them?
The one
on the right was Lyndon,
and the left was Johnson.
No, that was
your boobs we did.
No, your boobs
were Minnie and Mickey.
I remember that
because of Disney WorId.
And Felix.
Felix is what
we caIIed your...
(CAT SCREECHES)
BUCK: God damn kids.
Okay. Come on, you.
Come on,
get in the house.
What are you doing out here,
making all this noise?
Get in the house
where you belong.
Come on ! Come on !
Hey!
Who let the cat out?
MlLES: We don't have a cat.
Come on ! Get out!
Go on ! Shoo!
Hey!
(MAlZY LAUGHlNG)
Open up!
Miles?
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Hello.
Hi. May l please speak
to Buck Russell?
This is a friend of his
Chanice Kobolowski.
l'm sorry, Chanice.
He's not here right now.
Well, can you tell me
when he's gonna be back?
He went out with Marcie,
the lady who lives
across the street.
They usually
stay out pretty late.
Do you want to
leave a message?
No. There's no message.
There's no message.
Hot!
MARClE: ls there a big,
sexy guy in here?
Oh, please
don't let it be true.
Hi.
Oh, my God !
What are you doing?
The laundry.
What's it look like?
The washing machine's
still broken,
so l thought
l'd use the microwave.
Nuke them up, you know.
Heats them up pretty good, too.
lt kills the germs
and odors that they cause.
You don't know
what you're doing.
You're bored
out of your mind.
You need a little
adult supervision.
Excuse me?
(SOOTHlNG MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Come on.
l don't want to dance.
l don't feel like. . .
l'm not a dancer.
This is ridiculous.
l'm not gonna leave
unless you do.
Okay, l'll dance.
One dance, though.
That's it.
'Cause l really have to
take a nap and. . .
All right. One dance.
That's it.
(DOORBELL RlNGlNG)
Whoa!
What's this?
Oh ! Come on !
The dog is watching.
Come on.
What's that? Dirty Dancing?
Uh-huh.
You got the girl
by the neck.
Whoa. Dipped her.
Remember that?
Dips. Dips.
Am l bleeding?
No.
Will you get off?
My back!
Hello.
Stop it.
l mean it.
This is fun though,
isn't it?
l guess.
My aerobic
workout today.
Heart's beating
like a rabbit here.
Oh.
Yeah.
Hi, Chanice.
Surprise!
This is, um. . .
Marcie.
Yeah. Marcie,
and she lives
across the road.
She came over to. . .
Shut up, Buck.
That's a good idea.
ls this who you were
out with last night?
What?
l didn't go out last night.
Hey, look. Honest.
Honest. Honest.
l'm telling the truth.
You son of a bitch !
Don't say that, okay. Chanice.
Don't walk away. Chanice!
Chanice!
Hey, come here!
Come here, hon.
Chanice, wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
Let me explain !
Will you let me explain?
You're wrecking the driveway!
Chanice!
Come on !
l love you.
What flew up her nose?
You better go home,
okay, Marcie?
Pick up your records.
The party's over.
Okay?
So, l'll just go home
and wait for
the Federal Express man.
Good night, Uncle Buck.
Good night, sweetheart.
Good night.
Uncle Buck?
Yeah?
Got a minute?
l got lots of minutes.
Now that everything's
okay with my grandfather,
l want to go out
tomorrow night.
You can go crazy after
l leave. Until then,
l'm not letting you out.
You just can't find
any way to be cool,
can you?
You mean easy? No.
l mean decent.
You mean blind.
Who are you trying to
score points with,
my parents?
How many times
have they had you here
since we moved?
Try none until they
went up shit creek
and got stuck.
Get used on
your parents' time.
Hey, Buck!
Yeah.
Have a bad day today?
lt hurts when someone
screws with your life,
doesn't it?
Last call.
There you go.
A little for you,
a little for me.
Boy, people used to
say to me,
"Boy, Buck,
you are one lucky
son of a bitch.
"You got it made, Buck.
You got it made."
And l did.
They'd say,
"Oh, man, Buck,
look at you.
"You don't have any kids,
you don't have any wife.
"You don't have a desk,
you don't have an office.
"You don't have a boss
to worry about."
They were right.
l had it made.
Only thing now is, Perce,
nobody says that anymore.
Oh, boy.
But
it'll all be
better tomorrow.
Always is.
Because tomorrow,
we go to the track,
win some dough,
some serious dough.
Yeah.
Make a lot of money
tomorrow, kiddo.
You want a little pretzel
with your beer?
U. B. went to school
to pick you up, you know.
Tell U. B. when he gets home
that he lost, okay?
Lost what?
Just tell him.
He'll know what it means.
l'll see you guys Sunday.
What day is today?
Friday.
You know what that means.
Jumbo party.
You can put that
on a platter.
(CAR BACKFlRES)
U. B. is home.
BUCK: Tia! Tia!
You guys seen Tia?
She took a breeze, U. B.
And she promised me
she was going to look after
you guys this evening.
She promised me.
So much for promises.
Does anyone in this house
know how to keep a promise?
l know you two guys do.
l know.
l had somewhere important
to go to tonight.
This is how
l make my living.
This was very
important to me.
This was. . . My whole year
was based on tonight.
lt may be peanuts
to your dad
but it's my living.
l have no choice,
l don't care what your
parents are going to say.
l have to take you
with me tonight.
Where?
To a racetrack.
BUCK: Here we go.
You have to go
to the bathroom?
BOTH: Nope.
You sure?
BOTH: Yep.
This is going to
be fun, you know.
Beautiful horses,
interesting people.
And win some
serious coin, right?
Well, sometimes, yeah,
but that's not the real
reason people go there.
People go because of
the beautiful horses
and the colorful jockeys.
Bug picked up Tia?
Mmm-hmm.
And she said
she was going
to a party.
She said
she'd be back Sunday.
Must be a slumber party.
Hop in the back.
Get your belts on.
Let her go to
a party all weekend !
She's old enough
to know better.
Hell, she doesn't listen
to anybody anyway.
Damn kids.
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Yeah.
Kobolowski Tires.
Hi. lt's me.
Buck, can't you ever
take a hint?
Chanice, it's not about me.
l got a problem at the house.
I need somebody
to watch the kids.
No. l'll tell you
what you need.
Your horse fixer's
in town
and you need to
get to the track.
l ran into Rog.
See, he told me
all about it.
The idiot had the nerve
to ask me for a loan.
What's the matter?
You can't take children
with you when you're gonna
cheat on a horserace?
You got some religion
out there in the 'burbs?
l came close.
l had them in the car.
Can we put
personal problems
aside for a second?
Tia took off on me.
l was supposed to
pick her up after school.
She wasn't there.
What do you mean,
she ran away?
l guess. l don't know.
She's 1 5, she's angry,
she's confused,
and I need to find her.
Can you help me?
l'm really stuck, Chanice.
All right. All right.
l will help you because
there's kids involved
in this.
But as far as you
and l are concerned,
it is over.
However it has to be.
l'll be there.
Thank you.
For what it's worth,
l'm sorry.
Your car's on fire.
Car's on fire.
No, no, no.
lt's just a little oil.
l'm looking for a party
somewhere around here.
Oh, that's on
Totowa Lane.
My niece is there.
Our son's there.
Kids.
l don't think
you ought to go in there
with that hat on.
They'll kill you.
Really?
Thanks for the tip.
Yeah.
(GASPS)
l'm supposed to come over
and watch you.
Hi !
l'm Chanice Kobolowski.
l'm Uncle Buck's friend.
May l see your
driver's license,
ma'am?
Yeah.
Sure.
Good idea.
Here! l got it!
See? Look.
Look!
Can you please
take it out of there?
Take it out?
You okay?
Come on.
What's the matter?
(ALL SCREAM)
Coming through here.
How you doing?
Having a good time?
You seen a guy named
Bug around here?
l'm Tia Russell's uncle.
You girls know Tia?
No? She's kind of new.
l'm her uncle.
You haven't seen that Bug
around here, have you?
No.
Nice guy.
Hey! Hey!
Come back here with that!
How you doing?
Anybody seen Bug around here?
Hey, nice music.
Who's that?
The Grass Roots?
l'm kidding.
l know my music.
Stop it, please.
What the hell is that?
Hey, party time!
Let's get down here, huh?
You seen Bug around here?
You seen Bug?
That's good stuff.
Keep it up. Keep it up.
Nice work.
Hey, how you doing?
Excuse me.
Crowded, huh?
Get down, get down, get down.
l don't want to do this.
Just relax.
Hello, young fellow.
How are you?
l'm Tia Russell's uncle,
Buck Russell.
Have you seen
the bug around?
No? l'm looking for him.
You're Tia Russell's uncle?
Really?
Hey! Give me that!
Take my hat, you punk!
Don't mention it.
All right, pop.
Have you seen a guy named Bug?
Everybody knows Bug.
Hip, hip guy.
Let me through here,
will you?
Your mother know
you do that?
(KNOCKlNG ON DOOR)
Hey, this room's taken.
l want to go.
No, you don't.
(DOOR RATTLlNG)
That door opens,
l'm going to kick
somebody's ass!
Do you hear me?
Tia.
You were right.
Everything you said
would happen happened.
l don't want
to talk about it.
l just want
to get you home.
ls this a trick?
No.
You know what happened?
Yeah.
Are you going to tell
my parents about everything
that's been going on?
No.
Thanks.
l've been riding
your butt all week about
how you live your life.
l realize maybe somebody
should have been riding mine.
l'm probably the last guy
in the world you'd want
to help,
but l really could use your
advice, vis-a-vis Chanice.
l've been
stringing her along
for about eight years now.
Maybe you could figure out
what the hell is wrong
with me.
l did such a great job
earning your trust
and admiration,
l'm confused why l can't
do the same with Chanice.
You know there's
one family charity case
that loves you very much.
l'm sorry.
Hey, come on.
Nothing to be sorry about.
l'm just kind of glad
l got a chance to know
you again.
Did you do anything to Bug?
Oh, my God !
What did you do?
You shithead !
l could have suffocated here!
Um, do you know what
l'd like you to do?
Actually, you could be
doing both of us a favor.
l'd like you to apologize
to the lady, please.
l'm sorry!
Okay, asshole?
l don't know if
l told you this or not,
but l'm an amateur dentist?
Oh, yes. He is.
(LAUGHlNG EVlLLY)
l'm sorry.
Get him out of there.
Yeah?
lt was halfhearted.
We'll let him.
Come on, here we go.
l'm really sorry.
l'm sure you are.
Let me just get you. . .
l didn't mean
to hurt anybody.
There you go.
Oh, l'm sorry.
Shall we?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Well, come on back,
and l'll kick your ass, man !
Chicken shit! You're dead !
Shit.
l'm gonna sue
your balls off, man !
Why don't you come again?
Come on !
Come on, man !
l'm going to sue you
and l'm going to sue
your whole family!
Okay, pal.
Time for a golf lesson.
My dad's a lawyer, msn !
You're history!
A little fine wood.
Hey. What?
What? What are you doing, man?
Shit.
You're history, man !
You're wasted !
l'm gonna sue you
for everything
you've got, man !
You're gonna be broke!
So come on, come and get me!
You bastard ! Aah !
Yes, sir!
You son of a bitch !
That hurt!
Hey, hey, hey.
l'm not sorry,
all right?
l ain't sorry for shit!
What do you see
in that guy anyway?
l can't for the life of me
figure that one out.
Don't answer.
You don't have to.
l appreciate
the confession, Tia.
Thank you. Thanks a lot.
But my problems
with Buck
go a whole lot deeper
than a misunderstanding
with a neighborlady.
Don't you think
he loves you?
lf he does,
he'd never say it.
What if he did?
Then l would suspect
he needed a new set of tires.
Seriously.
You're very sweet
to talk about this
but l don't think
you understand
the bigger picture.
See, Buck's a charming man
who wants to remain
a boy forever.
Boy?
And at my age,
that doesn't make for
a lasting relationship.
l think he'd make
a wonderful husband
and father.
You do?
Oh, yeah.
My sister and brother
adore him.
He really
has changed since
he's been here this week.
He really has changed.
He's responsible
and caring and loving
and enthusiastic. . .
Energetic.
And energetic and
decent
(MUFFLED COUGH)
and kind
(COUGHlNG CONTlNUES)
and humble
and honest and forthright.
Sense of humor.
And he's really got
a great sense of humor.
Did he by any chance
put you up to this?
No! Oh, no.
Mmm-mmm.
No, l've just gathered this
from my own observations.
No?
lt's just the way he is.
Really?
Um !
(CLEARlNG THROAT)
Really?
Oh, yeah !
So unlike him.
Ow!
Check this out.
Hi, honey!
ls the coffee ready?
A little thirsty.
By the way, l have
told you l loved you,
and it wasn't for tires,
sweetheart.
lt was for shocks, remember?
Oh, are they sweethearts,
or what?
This one's
smart as a whip.
l'm going to miss
them like crazy.
They're beautiful children.
What happened to you?
Recessive gene,
skips every
nine generations.
l got it this time.
Mmm-hmm.
Tragic.
lt isn't so bad, is it?
What?
The house, the family,
the kids.
Oh, yeah.
No, it's great.
This is great.
We should have done this
a long time ago,
something like this,
you know, you and l.
(BOTH SCREAMlNG)
They're here!
What are we doing?
Well, your mother,
you see, and your sister
have to
sort some things out.
They have to
So we're going to be
very quiet for them.
So why don't we
put a button on it
like this
and a zipper, like that,
and a lock.
l can't talk at all.
l throw the key away.
lt's going to be
real different.
l promise.
l love you.
Shit!
MAlZY: Bye!
MlLES: Bye, Uncle Buck!
Well, could l get
out the door, please?
l'm going !
Well, this is heavy.
Bye!
Thanks again, Buck.
Next time you're downtown,
maybe we can go out for
a coffee.
Okay.
We really had a good time.
l know it's kind of
ridiculous.
We did leave the house
a little messy.
We did try our best.
You know, we're not
so good at. . .
Chanice.
What?
We're going home,
we're not dying.
l'm saying good-bye,
is that all right?
All right.
Nice guy, is he?
Tell the neighbors
we're really sorry
about having that thing
parked in the driveway
all week.
He's getting
a new company car
on Monday.
The hell l am !
The beast is good for
another 1 00,000 miles.
Yeah, well,
it's too bad
that you're not.
That's funny, Chanice.
That's good.
See what l put up with?
Don't drive fast.
l'm not fixing anymore
tickets for you.
BUCK: Wake up!
(AlR HORN BLOWlNG)
(BUCK LAUGHlNG)
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4sump
Help other users to choose the best subtitles